

#### INFO

- Baybay Leyte, Philippnes
- 09238485582
- ☑ janfrancisisrael@gmail.com
- www.digitaliron.com/jan\_tools
- **EXECUTE** December 27, 1988

#### SOCIAL

- **f** Facebook https://facebook.com/janfrancis.israel
- S Skype janfrancisisrael
- in Linkedin www.linkedin.com/in/janfrancisisrael

"Driven professional with broad technical skill set.

Excellent communicator experienced interpreting and implementing client and staff visions of new websites.

Known for ability to multi-task and juggle multiple pressing projects simultaneously, meeting all deadlines.

Thrives in environments that constantly embrace new technologies."

# JAN FRANCIS ISRAEL

**WEB DEVELOPER / DESIGNER** 



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2016 - 2016

## **AZTECBPO**SR WEB DEVELOPER

- Create ideas and insight for improving usability of our web tools
- Coordinated analysis, design, implementation and test of a large software system
- Designed new Features and Website Services
- Optimized the Application for Maximum Speed and Scalability
- Integrated user-facing elements developed by front-end developers with server side logic.

2015 - 2015

# **ASIAN GATEWAY COMMUNICATION SUPPORT** *IT ENGINEER*

- Maintained and Modify existed system
- Develop front end functionality of websites
- · Designing prototypes for apps and websites
- Creates WordPress themed websites
- Modify Wordpress theme and Plugins
- Convert Bootsrap to Dynamic Website

2013 - 2015

### AUTHOR SOLUTIONS INC. (FORMERLY XLIBRIS)

WEB AND GRAPHICS DESIGNER

- Creates WordPress themed website
- · Modifying and updating themes and plugins
- Migrations of websites to another web server and Web alterations
- Modifying and Restructure Database

2012 - 2013

#### FREELANCE

### WEBSITE DESIGNER/DEVELOPER, ILLUSTRATOR, GRAPHICS ARTIST

- Creates Websites using Wordpress/bootstrap and static pages
- Migrations of websites to another web server and Web alterations
- Design and Create book illustrations and other printed materials

2010 - 2012

## **AFFILIATED COMPUTER SERVICES**TRANSACTION PROCESSOR

- $\cdot$  Identify type of blue print
- Encode blue print details such as project title and class
- · QA for our teams work

O a

#### SKILLS AND EXPERTIZE

CREATIVE	PROGRAMMING
PHOTOSHOP	HTML/HTML5
ILLUSTRATOR	CSS/CSS3
FLASH	РНР
AFTER EFFECTS	JAVASCRIPT/JQUERY
ZBRUSH	SQL
	ANGULAR JS
	LARAVEL FRAMEWORK
	PYTHON
	NODE.JS

#### REFERENCES

Susiness Development Manager 63-906-401-3681

ROCHELLE ARCEO hr/admin staf 69-933-417-3478



#### **EDUCATION**

2006 - 2010 FRANCISCAN COLLEGE OF IMMACULATE CONCEPTION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

2001 - 2005 FRANCISCAN COLLEGE OF IMMACULATE CONCEPTION SECONDARY

1995 - 2001 BAYBAY NORTH CENTRAL SCHOOL PRIMARY



#### **KEY COMPETENCIES**

- Awareness of the Web Development industry, and new technologies.
- Strategically thinking through all parts of the design process Knowledge of international web standards and protocols.
- Able to organise own workload effectively and prioritise tasks.
- Can quickly understand business requirements and then translate these into functional requirements
- Can manage multiple projects in a fast-paced, deadline-driven environment.
- Adaptable and able to quickly pick up new techniques.
- Passionate about doing a good job.
- First rate interpersonal and communication skills, able to easily interact with fellow developers and customers alike
- Comfortable with being the 'go to' person in a company.
- Strongly committed to all projects from inception right through to the end.
- Confident, friendly and easy to get along with